ruvilla.com 2017-10-01

# Privacy Policy | VILLA

## Our Commitment to Privacy

At VILLA, we value our customers and respect your privacy. We collect information about you in our stores and through our websites in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, contests and promotions. As described in this policy, we may share your information under certain circumstances, with third parties that provide services on our behalf or with whom we have partnered to offer a particular product or service.

This policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it, and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. If our information practices change, we will post an updated policy on our website. You can tell if the policy has changed by checking the revision date that appears above. You may exercise your choices about how we collect and use your information consistent with this policy at any time.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below.

### What kind of information does VILLA collect?

We may collect personal information from you, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, credit card number, gender, birthday, personal interests, etc., when you visit one of our websites or stores, place an order online or by phone, make an in-store purchase, save your information with us online, contact us with a question or concern, or participate in a contest, promotion, or survey. We maintain a record of your product interests and the purchases you make online or by phone and in our stores.

### How does VILLA use my information?

We may use your personal information in the following ways:

  * To process and fulfill your order, including to send you emails to confirm your order status and shipment
  * To communicate with you and to send you information by email, postal mail, telephone, text message, or other means about our products, services, contests, and promotions, unless you have directed us not to contact you with promotional communications
  * To administer and fulfill our contests and other promotions
  * To help us learn more about your shopping preferences
  * To help us address problems with and improve our site design, products and services
  * To enhance your shopping experience
  * To analyze trends and statistics
  * To protect the security or integrity of our websites and our business
  * To contact you if necessary

You always have the choice not to receive marketing information or calls. For instructions on opting out, please see the section entitled, "How do I make choices about receiving promotional communications?", below.

### Does VILLA share my information?

We may share your personal information in the following ways:

  * We may share your information with our service providers who manage our customer information and perform services on our behalf, such as fulfilling promotions, sending communications to our customers, conducting surveys, etc. We do not authorize any of these service providers to make any other use or disclosure of your information.
  * We may share your information when we team up with another company to offer or provide products, services, contests, or promotions to our customers.
  * We may share information about you if necessary, in our good faith judgment, to comply with laws or regulations or in response to a valid subpoena, order, or government request, or to protect the rights of VILLA or others.

In the unlikely event of a sale or merger of VILLA, our customers' personal information and other information we have collected as described in this policy may be among the transferred business assets.

### How do I access or change my information?

You can review and change certain personal information related to your use of our online sites (such as your name and contact information). To access your information at VILLA's website, simply sign in to your account using your email address and password, and you will be able to edit your personal information in your account profile.

You can also ask us to update your personal information by contacting us as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below. Please note that any request to update your personal information may take up to 10 days for your email request and 6-8 weeks for your postal mail request.

### How do I make choices about receiving promotional communications?

VILLA wants to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive promotional information, such as information about special offers and sales events, you can let us know by contacting our customer service as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below.

Please be sure to include your full name and the email address you used when you registered with or made a purchase from VILLA. If you ask us to remove your name and address from promotional lists, we will maintain your name in a "do not contact" file to ensure that we can honor your request. It may take up to 10 days to process your email request and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request, during which period you may continue to receive communications from VILLA.

If you change your mind, you can start receiving promotional communications from us again by logging into your online account and changing your preferences, by signing up when you visit our websites or our stores or when you enter a sweepstakes or contest, or by contacting customer service.

Please note that when you make an online purchase from us, we will continue to confirm your order status and shipment by email. We may also need to contact you via telephone, email or postal mail with questions or information regarding your order.

### How does VILLA protect kids' privacy?

VILLA is concerned about the privacy and safety of children when they use the Internet. We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information online from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. Our websites are general audience sites and are not targeted to or intended for use by children.

### How does VILLA use cookies and other tracking technologies?

Our websites use "cookies," which are small data files that are stored on your computer when you visit a website. Cookies enable you to shop on our websites and may be used in a variety of ways to enhance or personalize your online browsing and shopping experience.

For example, we may use cookies to enable you to use certain website features, remember the items in your shopping cart, store your preferences, recognize you when you return to our website, track your orders, and monitor and maintain information about your use of our websites.

You can set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether or not to accept it. If you do not accept cookies, however, you will not be able to access your account information or make purchases on our websites.

We may combine the information we collect through cookies with other information we have collected from and about you. This information may be used to improve our websites, to personalize your online experience, to tailor our communications with you, to determine the effectiveness of our advertising, and for other internal business purposes.

### How do I know my personal information is secure?

We do our best to provide you with a safe and convenient shopping experience. We have in place certain physical, electronic, and managerial safeguards to protect the security and privacy of your personal information.

When you enter your personal information on our websites, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your information as it is transmitted to us. To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit personal financial information, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. To double-check for security, look at the URL or Location line of your browser. If you have accessed a secure server, the first characters of the address in that line should change from "http" to "https."

If for any reason you cannot access the secure server, or if you're not quite comfortable shopping online at any of our websites, please feel free to place your order with us by telephone at the number listed in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below.

### What is "phishing"?

"Phishing" is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an email that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through email.

### I received a suspicious email from VILLA regarding an order I did not place. What should I do?

For your protection, do not click links or open any files attached to suspicious, unsolicited emails. If you believe your personal computer has been compromised as a result of the scam, please consult an IT professional. For more information, contact the FBI's Internet Crimes Complaint Center:<http://www.ic3.gov/default.aspx>.

### I responded to an online job posting for a VILLA job that requires me to upload personal financial information. Is this part of your hiring process?

No. VILLA does not ask prospective job applicants for information about their bank accounts, credit history or passwords to financial accounts. If you are asked for personal financial or security information in response to a job application, this is likely a fraudulent job listing hosted by spammers posing as VILLA to mislead job applicants. You can validate all VILLA job postings on [www.ruvilla.com/careers](http://www.ruvilla.com/careers). If you receive this type of suspicious email activity, please alert the FBI's Internet Crimes Complaint Center:<http://www.ic3.gov/default.aspx>

### What about links to other websites?

For your convenience and information, our websites may contain links to other sites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked site. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any site that you access through our sites.

### How do I contact you?

For questions about our privacy policy, to make choices about receiving promotional communications, to update your personal information, or to place an order, you can contact VILLA by email, telephone, or postal mail:

VILLA Internet Customer Service

1926 Arch Street, 3R,  
Philadelphia, PA 19103

Phone 844 RUVILLA | 844-788-4552  
Fax (215) 279-5599
